Resume Nilesh Makwana

E-Mail ID – Nileshsm501@gmail.com

Mobile - 91 9998004250



Career Objective:

Server/System/Could Administrator, Team Leader, Asset & Vendor Management Overall 15+ years' Experience in the 3 Reputed MNC Companies and Small Company as a Sr. IT Executive and Team Leader. Direct reporting to Company HOD. I have ability to IT Assistant Manager, IT Manager, Service Delivery Manager and many-more.

Professional Qualification:

- MCSA (Microsoft Certified Systems Administrator) from Jetking Vadodara 2008.
- Diploma in computer hardware and networking from Jetking Vadodara 2007

Academic Qualification:

- Bachelor of commerce from Dr.C.V.Raman University in 2015.
- High School Certificate from Gujarat board with first division in 2005.
- Secondary School Certificate from Gujarat Board with first division in 2003.

Work Experience

❖ Larsen and Toubro India Ltd. On payroll of Hitachi India P Ltd.

As a Sr. IT Executive L2 @ 7th Now 2022 to Present

Ethics InfoTech LLP.

As a System/Server administrator @11th Feb 2021 to 31 Oct 2022.

Nielsen Inda P Ltd. On payroll of Randstad India P Ltd.

As a Team Lead @ 1st March 2016 to 31st Oct 2019.

♦ Bombardier Inda P Ltd. On payroll of PC Solution P Ltd.

As a Technical Support Engineer @ 1st June 2011 to 29th Feb 2016

IT Source Ltd.

As a Field Support Engineer @ 6th Dec 2009 to 31 May 2011

ABB India Ltd. On payroll of Pattani computer Ltd

As a Customer Support Engineer @ 16th Jan 2008 to 4 Dec 2009

Technical Skills.

- Window Server Support Active Directory, DNS, DHCP, GPO, ERP & SAP, Backup & Restore, VMware & Hyper-V and could support (Azure could) and RDP support or much more support.
- Could Support / Office 365 Email ID creation, Delectation, Modification, Data Backup & Restore, Data Migration to Windows Could and many more.
- Network Support Configuration, Management & Troubleshoot of Switch, Router, Firewall and Wi-Fi, LAN, MAN, WAN network & much more support.
- Software Support All types of software/Application installation, Troubleshooting, and Activation.
- Team Leader, Asset Management & Inventory and Vendor Management.
- Working on ticketing SLA tool (Remedy, Service Now and SIM)
- Ability to learn new functions & executes them with full enthusiasm.
- Excellent interpersonal communication skills along with a professional attitude and confidence to meet the demands of the industry.
 - I have been worked in 3 MNC companies with users interact likes VIP users, VVIP users, MD Level users, and foreigner user.
 - Hardware support & CCTV Troubleshooting and Maintenance.
 - Asset Inventory & Management, Vendor Management, Attendance record.
 - All Windows OS, Linux OS, Ubuntu OS, Mac OS, Raspberry OS work experience.
 - Remote support all over India and out of India

Personal details:

Full Name: Nilesh S. Makwana

Father's Name: Sureshbhai B Makwana

Date of Birth: 8 of April 1985

Nationality: Indian

Gender: Male

Marital status: Married

Language Know: Gujarati, English & Hindi

Biggest Strength: Confidence, Challenging Job & Positive Attitude.

Passport No.: S7574636

Permanent Address: B/49 Parnkuter Society No.1, Opp Nilamber Township, Nr.

Narayana School road, Gurukul crossroad, Waghodia road, Vadodara.

Date: Yours Faithfully Place: Vadodara Nilesh Makwana